McCann Postcard Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
McCann Postcard Collection
1901 - 1908
NPkMC-223-083
1 Linear Foot
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Agnes McCann
The McCann Postcard Collection consists of a series of postcards from the friends and family of the McCann’s around the world from the years 1901- 1908 as well as a book on a car’s transcontinental journey.
Collection Overview
The McCann Postcard Collection consists of various postcards sent to Agnes and her family between 1901 and 1908 and a book describing the transcontinental journey of the Mitchell Ranger.
The McCann Postcard Collection was loaned to Marist College by John Gartland Jr.
Historical Note
Agnes McCann lived with her family in Poughkeepsie, New York. Her brother, James J. McCann, took over the family feed and grain store and made millions investing in the stock market. James McCann became a philanthropist donating money to the local community and establishing the McCann Foundation which continues to help the community. Agnes and her sister Mary traveled extensively and the postcard collection reflects correspondence between themselves, their family, and friends.
There are no restrictions on this collection
Arrangement of the Collection
These records are organized into two series: 1) Postcards collected by Agnes McCann and 2) Miscellaneous
Materials retain their original order
- 1. Postcards collected by Agnes McCann, 1; 1 linear feet Box: 1 Folder: 1 Number of items: 420
  Series contains a collection of 420 postcards saved by Agnes McCann. Postcards are arranged in original order as found in the album, where they were displayed, with six postcards to a page.
  Original Order
  - Pulvinare Dell’Arena. Arch. Bongi. 1906., 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Milano, Duomo e Piazza. Mar. 15, 1906., 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Gli Argini Al Po. 1906., 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Crater of Kilauea, Hawaii (as seen from Volcano House.) Aug. 5, 1904., 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vesuvio in Eruzione. 1906., 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Grand Canyon of Arizona, From O’Neill’s Point. Sep. 1904., 6 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - St. Luke’s Hospital, Newburgh, N.Y. Aug. 1906., 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Egypte. Village arabe., 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Milano, Interno Galleria. Sep. 30, 1905., 9 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Milano, Monumento a Camillo Cavour. 1905., 10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ingressa Alla Villa. 1906., 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Government Building, Formerly the Royal Palace. Hawaiian Islands. Jul. 1904., 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Milano Ottagono della Galleria Vittorio Emanuele. Mar. 29, 1906., 13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Soldiers’ and Sailors’ Monument, N.Y City. Jul. 12, 1906., 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Lyndhurst.” Residence of Miss Helen M. Gould. Tarrytown, N.Y. Mar. 24., 15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Entrance to Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Apr. 5, 1906., 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - United States Post Office, Cleveland, Ohio. Jul. 25, 1906., 17 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Glen Falls, Cairo, N.Y., 18 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Eads Bridge, St. Louis. Aug. 2, 1905., 19 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Eastman College and High School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Aug. 9, 1905., 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Landing of “The Albany,” Kingston Point, N.Y., 21 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Old Van Rensselaer House where Yankee Doodle was written. Jun. 22, 1906., 22 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Palisades from Old Dock, Englewood, N.J. 1905., 23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Bridge from N.Y City. Mar. 1, 1905., 24 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bloomingdale, White Plains, N.Y. Aug. 14, 1905., 25 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Harbor, Yorktown, V.A. Jul. 28, 1904., 26 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Albany, N.Y. Aug. 1, 1906., 27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Presbyterian Church, Englewood, N.J. Oct. 10, 1905., 28 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bird’s Eye View of Coney Island by Night. May 27, 1906., 29 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Milano, Arco della Pace. 1906., 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Il Lago. Feb. 1906., 31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Milano, Corso Vittorio Emanuele. Jul. 20, 1906, 32 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Castle, New Rochelle, N.Y. Jan. 11, 1906., 33 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stratford on Avon. Early Home of John Harvard’s Mother. Jun. 1905., 34 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - City Hall Park from Broadway, N.Y., 35 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Guthrie’s Mill, Norwalk, Conn. Apr. 18, 1906., 36 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - City Hall, Brooklyn. 1905., 37 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Marlborough House, Atlantic City, N.J. Sep. 5, 1905., 38 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Greater New York. Broad Street and Stock Exchange. May 24, 1905., 39 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Graduating Class, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Aug. 3, 1905., 40 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Observatory Downing Park, Newburgh, N.Y. Aug. 20, 1906., 41 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Along the Shore of Chautauqua Lake. 1906., 42 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “To Mine Sweetheart.” Feb. 13, 1908., 43 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hotel Ponce de Leon, St. Augustine Fla. Apr. 6, 1904., 44 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Floral Steps, Prospect Park, Brooklyn, N.Y. Sep 9, 1905., 45 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Fountain, White Plains, N.Y. Aug 19, 1905., 46 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “I Would like to meet you.” (Riddle card.) Aug. 18, 1905., 47 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Tent Life at Ocean Grove.” Aug. 16, 1904., 48 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Belmar, N.J, Shark River. Aug. 18, 1905., 49 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Buttermilk Falls and Cranstons,” Hudson River. Jul 2?. 1905., 50 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Beach and Boardwalk, Ashbury Park. Aug. 15, 1905., 51 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Spring Lake, N.J. Aug. 22, 1905., 52 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sugarloaf Mountain, Hudson River Highlands. Aug 1905., 53 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - United States Hotel, Far Rockaway, L.I. 1905., 54 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Riverside Drive, New York. Jul. 6, 1905., 55 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - East Rock, New Haven, Conn. Aug. 16, 1904., 56 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University Circle, Cleveland, Ohio. Jun. 5, 1906., 57 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General U.S. Grant Monument and Tomb, New York. Jul. 17, 1905., 58 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Park Lake Bridge, Washington Park. Jul. 28, 1906., 59 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - City Hall, Albany, N.Y. Jul. 28, 1906., 60 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Catskill Mountains: View of the parks at Haines Falls, N.Y. Aug. 10, 1905., 61 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Bathing Place, Lake Mohonk, N.Y. Jul. 1906., 62 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Beach, Far Rockaway, L.I. Jul. 1905., 63 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Saratoga Springs, N.Y., Grand Union Hotel. Jul. 1906., 64 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Kingston Point Park, Kingston, N.Y. Jul. 22, 190?., 65 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Kingston Point, Hudson River. Aug. 1906., 66 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Fountain, Staatsburg, N.Y. Mar. 10, 1906., 67 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, N.Y. City. Oct. 1904., 68 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Saratoga Lake, Saratoga, N.Y. Aug. 20, 1904., 69 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Entrance to Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Sep. 24, 190?., 70 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Entrance to Church of Divine Compassion, White Plains, N.Y. Jun. 14, 1905., 71 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Saratoga Springs, N.Y., Congress Spring Park. Aug. 26, 1905., 72 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled. Aug. 11, 1906., 73 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Old Mill Wheel, Rhinebeck, N.Y., 74 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Springfield, Ill. State Arsenal. Aug. 1905., 75 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Birdseye View of Mattewan and Fishkill Landing. Newburgh in the Distance. From Mt. Beacon, N.Y. Jul. 29, 1904., 76 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Catskills, Haines Falls. Aug. 8, 1905., 77 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Old Landmark. Jul. 1905., 78 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rumsen Road on the Jersey Coast. Aug. 1906., 79 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Kingston Point, N.Y. showing Lagoons and Sand Beach. Aug. 18, 1906., 80 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Shady Drive, Mohonk Lake, N.Y. Jul. 4, 1905., 81 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled. Sep. 15, 1905., 82 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Teddy’s.” Dec. 190?., 83 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “To My Sweetheart.” Feb. 190?., 84 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Riding Girl. Aug., 85 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled. (Woman in Blue Dress.) Oct. 29, 1907., 86 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled. (Woman in yellow and black uniform.) Nov. 5, 1905., 87 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Blue Ribbon Winner.” Jul. 5, 1905., 88 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “What It Leads To.” Sep. 14, 1905., 89 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vassar College. Mar. 12, 1906., 90 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Toast.”, 91 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “July 4th, A Toast.”, 92 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ilitary Girl.” Dec. 6, 1905., 93 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Toast.” Jul. 19., 94 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Kissogram. Jul. 6, 1906., 95 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Suburban Girl. Feb. 14, 1906., 96 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Bit of Gossip. Sep. 30, 1905., 97 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Hello-ee! How you like-ee sail-ee?’ May 27, 1905., 98 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - St. Patrick’s Day Telegram. Mar. 17, 1906., 99 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Buster Brown.” Feb. 13, 1906., 100 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not labeled. (Halloween.) 1905., 101 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “This is No Fish Story.” Jul. 9, 1905., 102 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Sayin’ Nothing’.” Jul. 29, 1905., 103 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Sayin’ Nothin’.” Jul. 24, 1905., 104 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “The Whole Dam Family.” May 16, 1905., 105 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Dark Corner in Watermelon. Aug. 14, 1905., 106 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “To My Valentine.” Feb., 107 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Now, Will you Be Good!” Apr. 1906., 108 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Bank of Love Unlimited.”, 109 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Easter Joys be Thine.” Apr. 22, 1905., 110 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Easter Greetings.” Apr. 13, 1906., 111 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled. Apr. 22., 112 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Easter Greetings.” Apr. 14, 1906., 113 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “You are a Peach.” Feb., 114 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not labeled. May 13, 1905., 115 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “With Christmas Greetings.” Dec. 1904., 116 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Antico Refettorio di St. Maria delle Grazie- II. Cenacolo, celebre affresco di Leonardo da Vinci. Milano., 117 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Easter Joy be Thine.” Apr. 14, 1906., 118 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Happy Easter.” Apr. 22, 190?., 119 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Holy Happy Easter be Thine.” Apr. 14, 1906., 120 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Post Office, Newburgh, N.Y. Oct. 21, 1907., 121 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Happy New Year.” Dec. 30, 1904., 122 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Salutation and Greeting to You all.” Apr. 14, 1906., 123 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not labeled.(Ethel Parkinson.) May 11, 1906., 124 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not labeled. (M. Sowerby.) May 9, 1906., 125 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Bright and Happy Christmas.” Dec. 23, 1905., 126 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Merry Christmas.” Dec. 22, 1905., 127 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Happy New Year.” Jan. 1906., 128 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Happy New Year, 1906.” Dec. 31, 1906., 129 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Wishing You a Merry Christmas.” Dec. 23, 1905., 130 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “It is not every couple that is a pair.” Dec. 24, 1904., 131 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Buon Natale.” Dec. 30, 1905., 132 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “For the sake of Auld Lang ‘Syne.” Dec. 25, 1905., 133 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Easter Greetings.” Apr. 14, 190?., 134 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “It’s just horrid, Bertie, to think of living in a flat…” Aug. 1906., 135 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Was that you I kissed in the conservatory…” Mar. 3, 1906., 136 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Wasn’t there any time while you were making love to me…’ Aug. 1906., 137 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Cozy Corner. Oct. 1, 1905., 138 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Another Monopoly. Jan. 19, 1906., 139 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “The College Widow.”, 140 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Auto Girl. Apr. 1907., 141 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Miss Cleveland. Jul. 13, 1906., 142 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Thursday., 143 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Wednesday. July. 11, 1906., 144 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “The Last Jump.” Jul. 12, 1905., 145 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Having Touch of High Life.” Jul. 13, 1906., 146 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not labeled. (Flohri.) Aug. 29, 1905., 147 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “The Automobile Fiend.” Feb. 190?., 148 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not labeled. (Lance Thackery.) Aug. 25., 149 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Buster Brown and His Bubble.” “A Smooth Bit of Road.” Jul 21., 150 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “If you can’t come- write us.” Oct. 13, 1905., 151 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not labeled. (Ethel Parkinson.) May 22, 1906., 152 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “I’ve Not Much To Crow About.”, 153 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Christ Church P.E. and Rectory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y.” Aug. 11, 1905., 154 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yonkers, N.Y. Alta Ave. North. May 9, 1906., 155 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not labeled. Oct. 26, 1905., 156 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Down the Rivers, O’er the Prairies, Came the Warriors of the Nations.” Aug. 3, 1905., 157 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aerial Swing, Luna Park, Coney Island, N.Y. Jul. 18, 1905., 158 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dreamland: The Tramp. Coney Island, N.Y. Jul. 14, 1905., 159 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dreamland: Restaurant and Music Pavilion. Coney Island, N.Y. Jul. 12, 1905., 160 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Luna Park, Coney Island. Jul. 10, 1905., 161 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dreamland: Miniature Railway, Coney Island, N.Y. Jul. 10, 1905., 162 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Night Scene at Luna Park, N.Y. Aug. 31, 1904., 163 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Peekskill state camp, Peekskill, N.Y. Jun. 18, 1905., 164 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Indian Life Near Digby. Aug. 18, 1906., 165 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - View of State Military Camp, Peekskill, N.Y. from the Tents of the Young Men’s Christian Association. Jun. 20, 1905., 166 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Attention!” Jun. 19, 1905., 167 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “The Girl I Left Behind Me.” Jun. 21, 1905., 168 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “How D’You Like My New Lid?” Nov. 30, 1905., 169 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “New York, 92 Miles.”, 170 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Statue of Liberty, N.Y. City. Nov. 23, 1904., 171 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Flatiron Building, N.Y. City. Dec. 2, 1904., 172 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 13th Regiment Armory, Brooklyn, N.Y. May 5, 1906., 173 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Washington Arch, N.Y. City. Jun.10, 1905., 174 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Mall, Central Park, New York. Oct. 1905., 175 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Grant’s Tomb, New York. Jul. 22, 1906., 176 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mohonk Lake, N.Y. Moonlight Scene from Porte Cochere, Showing Lake and Sky Top. Jul. 1906., 177 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chudleigh Falls, Devon. Sep. 22, 1906., 178 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Big Tow.” Feb. 5, 1906., 179 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cavalry Drill, West Point, N.Y. Jul. 29, 1906., 180 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Manhattan Beach Hotel. Aug. 6, 1904., 181 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Pine Bluff, Mohonk Lake N.Y. Aug. 31, 1904., 182 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Main Street, Buffalo, N.Y. Sep. 10, 1905., 183 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Gananoque Inn, Gananoque, Thousand Islands, Canada. Aug. 15, 1903., 184 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bank of the Metropolis and Decker Bldg; Broadway& 16th St. New York, Jun. 7, 1905., 185 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Kingston, N.Y. Senate House. Sep. 5., 186 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Capitol, Albany, N.Y. Aug. 15, 1904., 187 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Along the Banks of the Hudson River. Mar. 5, 1906., 188 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - West Side Park, Paterson, N.J. Oct. 1905., 189 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Catskills, Labelle Falls, Aug. 3, 1904., 190 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - East Side Park, Paterson, N.J. Sep. 2, 1905., 191 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Greetings From Beacon Mountain. Washington’s Headquarters, Newburgh. Jul. 1905., 192 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - View of Middletown, N.Y. Jun. 16, 1908., 193 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Greetings from Tarrytown, N.Y. Old Dutch Church-1852. Sep. 16, 1904., 194 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lily Cove, Lake Washinee, Twin Lakes, Conn. Aug. 16, 1905., 195 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lake Mohonk, Mohonk Lake, Ulster Co., N.Y. Jun. 5, 1905., 196 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Union League Club, Brooklyn, N.Y. Sep. 2, 1905., 197 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Graduating Class. Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Aug. 14, 1905., 198 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fireproof Building, Mohonk Lake, N.Y. Jun. 5, 1905., 199 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Get Wise Come to Lake George.” Aug. 19, 1905., 200 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Railroad Station and Boat Landing, Kingston Point, N.Y., 201 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Seltzer’s Landing, Twin Lakes, Conn. Aug. 24, 1906., 202 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Interiors of the Old Senate House, Kingston. Aug. 22, 1904., 203 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Reformed Church, Rhinebeck, N.Y. Oct. 6, 1905., 204 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adirondack Inn, Sacandaga Park, N.Y. Aug. 20, 1906., 205 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Birdseye View of Matteawan and Fishkill Landing. Newburgh in the Distance. From Mt. Beacon, N.Y-Aug 8, 1905., 206 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lake Kensico, Kensico. Aug.30, 1905., 207 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - F.M. Lupton Summer residence, Mattituck, L.I. (J.H. Brown, Publisher) Sep 5, 1906?., 208 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “The Castle,” New Rochelle. N.Y. 3/06., 209 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Old Oak on the Island. Twin Lakes, Conn. Aug.17, 1905., 210 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Rensselaer. Troy, N.Y. Sept. 30, 1905., 211 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Soldiers’ Monument on Broadway, White Plains, N.Y. Sept. 25, 1905., 212 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Cove, Mattituck. Sept.5, 1906., 213 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1827. Old Dutch Reformed Church, Town Clock, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Nov. 28, 1905., 214 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “The Fountain,” Staatsburg, N.Y. (Miles Hughes.) Jul, 1905, 215 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - R.C. Franciscan Convent, Peekskill, N.Y. Jun 30, 1905., 216 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hudson River Day Line. Aug.8, 1905., 217 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Hudson River Day Line. Aug. 9, 1905., 218 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - St. Margaret’s Church, Staatsburg, N.Y. Jul., 1905., 219 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - White Plains High School, White Plains, N.Y. Jul.24, 1905., 220 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Boating on Verona Lake. Jul., 1905., 221 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “We’ve got our eyes on you.” Aug.5, 1905., 222 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “On the Clarion.?” Johnsonburg, P.A. Sept. 20, 1905., 223 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Casino, Ashbury Park, N.J. Aug.7, 1906., 224 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - St. John’s R.C. Church, White Plains, N.Y. June 13, 1905., 225 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Keeley Institute, White Plains, N.Y. Sept.23, 1905., 226 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - View of Old Iron Pier, Rockaway Beach, N.Y. Aug 7, 1905?., 227 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Arcade. Cleveland, Ohio. Jul.26, 1906., 228 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vineyard Avenue. Highland, N.Y. Feb.26, 1906., 229 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Scene in Prospect Park, Brooklyn, N.Y. Sept.5, 1907., 230 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General Grant’s Log Cabin, Fairmont Park, Philadelphia, P.A. Aug.16, 1906., 231 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - R.J. State Capitol, Providence, R.J. 1905., 232 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Temperance Outfit. Nov.? 1904., 233 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bucknell Institute, Lewisburg, P.A. June 23, 1904., 234 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General View of Kingston Point, N.Y., 235 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - McGlynn Cottage, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Dec2, 190?., 236 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Government Building. Pan American Exposition 1901, Buffalo, N.Y. Jul.18, 1901., 237 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hotel Ausable Chasm. Aug.18, 1905., 238 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lock Haven, P.A. Susquehanna River and Island North of Lock Haven. Dec.8, 1905., 239 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Main Street, Lock Haven, P.A. 1905., 240 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Flower Beds, Lake Mohonk House. Aug. 7, 1905., 241 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Auditorium Hotel and Annex, Chicago.Oct.15, 1905., 242 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clayton Club, Clayton, Thousand Islands, N.Y. Aug 15, 1905., 243 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chateau Frontenac from Dufferin Terrace. Quebec. Aug. 24, 1905., 244 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Murray Bay, The Manoir- Richelieu. Aug. 11, 1905., 245 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Keeley Institute, White Plains, N.Y. Sept. 8, 1905., 246 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - One of the Docks, Eastport, Maine. High Tide, Showing 28 feet rise of tides., 247 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Pick of the Fleet, Sardine Carriers, Eastport, Maine., 248 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hudson River Day Line., 249 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Catskills, Old Stone Bridge. Aug. 7, 1905., 250 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Night Scene of Dreamland, Coney Island, N.Y. Sept. 12, 1904., 251 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Providence, R.I., Gates, Roger Williams Park. Sept. 25, 1905., 252 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. May 25, 1904., 253 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Castle, Tarrytown, N.Y. Mar. 28, 1905., 254 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Speedway, N.Y. Oct. 26, 1904., 255 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Shooting the Chutes, Luna Park, Coney Island, N.Y. Sept. 12, 1904., 256 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Pan-American Exposition, 1901, Buffalo, N.Y. Sept. 13, 1901., 257 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lafayette Headquarters, White Plains, N.Y. Aug 25, 1905., 258 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rustic Bridge, Spring Lake, N.J. Aug. 17, 1904., 259 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - On the Hudson By Moonlight. Jun 2?, 1905., 260 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Y.M.C.A., White Plains, N.Y. June 13, 1905., 261 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Milano, La Cathedrale. Sept. 30, 190?., 262 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Gardens, Lake Mohonk House, N.Y. Jun. 23, 1906., 263 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Barclay Street Ferry Entrance, Hoboken, N.J. Sept. 11, 1905., 264 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Traymore Hotel, Atlantic City. Aug. 27, 1905., 265 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bloomingdale, White Plains, N.Y. Sept. 8, 1905., 266 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - San Gabriel Mission, C.A. Sept. 2, 1904., 267 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled. Jun. 14, 1905., 268 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Berkshire Inn, Great Barrington, Mass. May 30, 1904., 269 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rip Van Winkle. The Catskills. Aug. 9, 1905., 270 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Popular N.W Arm Rowing Club. Halifax, N.S. Aug 26, 1906., 271 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Viale Del Pioppi. Feb. 18, 1906., 272 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Highland School, Highland, N.Y. Feb. 27, 1906., 273 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Parc Royal de Laeken. Dec. 13, 1903., 274 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - New Galen Hotel, Atlantic City. Aug. 1905., 275 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Southern Gate of the Hudson Highlands. Aug. 16, 1906., 276 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Grand Flume Below Rapids, Ausable Chasm, N.Y. Aug 21, 1905., 277 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Newburg on the Hudson. Jul. 12, 1905., 278 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Crossman Hotel, Thousand Islands, N.Y. Aug. 17, 1905., 279 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fawns Leap- Catskill Mountains, N.Y. Aug. 8, 1905., 280 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Last Elm, Military Park, Newark, N.J. Apr. 7, 1906., 281 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bird’s eye view of Ellicott Square, Buffalo, N.Y. Dec. 2, 1905., 282 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Prospect Point- Niagara Falls. Dec. 2, 1905., 283 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Convention Ball, Knights of Columbus., 284 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bridge at Elmont, Highland, N.Y. Sep. 19, 1906., 285 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Greetings From New York. Nov. 23, 1904., 286 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - St. Patrick’s Cathedral, N.Y City. Dec. 2, 1904., 287 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Twenty-third Street Station, Underground Road, New York. Aug. 7, 1905., 288 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Washington Bridge and Speedway, New York., 289 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - West Point, Rapid Fire Gun Drill. Nov., 1906., 290 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Post Office, Broadway, N.Y. Jan. 10, 905., 291 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Dear love”- E. Curtis. Feb. 15, 190?., 292 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled. Man, Woman, and Cupid in Garden. Sep. 23, 1906., 293 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - World’s Fair. “I will meet you at Dreamland by the Sea.” Sep. 11, 1904., 294 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Happy New Year. Jan. ?, 1906., 295 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “This is no Fish Story.” Aug. 18, 1905., 296 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Wishing You Christmas Cheer.” Dec. 25, 1905., 297 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Bright New Year.” Dec. 30, 1904., 298 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Happy Easter.” (Basket with purple flowers.) Apr. 22, 19?., 299 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Buon Natale.” (Branch with pinecones.) Dec. 1905., 300 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “All Easter Happiness be Thine.” April 23, 1905., 301 (Box 1, Folder 1)